

PERSONAL

Birthday : 14th January 2001

Relationship : Single
Nationality : Filipino

Languages : English, Filipino, Bisaya

SKILLS

BROADCASTING WRITING PHOTOGRAPHY

SOFTWARE & LANGUAGES

PHOTOSHOP
CANVA
MS OFFICE
HTML
CSS
JAVASCRIPT

CONTACT



+63 938 476 2497



luaponinbaquero@gmail.com



Purok 5, Sal-ing, Balilihan, Bohol

PAUL BAQUERO

BS Information and Technology Student

PROFILE

I'm a 4th year Bachelor of Arts in information Technology Student of Bohol Island State University - Balilihan Campus. I am a student journalist with a 7 years of experience, most recently as a Editor-in-Chief of The Campus Access the official school publication of BISU Balilihan campus. My area of expertise is writing and editing articles for the school publication. I also layouts and capture some of the posts and photos of the publication. I am currently managing the social media platform of the of the Campus Access particularly its official facebook page. I am also the Vice President of the Supreme Student Government of BISU Balilihan, and it helps me to mold and develop my communication and leadership skills.

Education

PRIMARY EDUCATION

SAL-ING ELEMENTARY SCHOOL Sal-ing, Balilihan, Bohol 2006-2010

CAMP ABELON ELEMENTARY SCHOOL Pagadian City, Zamboanga Del Sur 2010 -2012

TERTIARY

BOHOL ISLAND STATE UNIVERSITY Balilihan Campus Magsija, Balilihan, Bohol 2019 - Present

SECONDARY

HOLY CHILD ACADEMY
Pagadian City, Zamboanga Del Sur
2012-2017

SAINT COLUMBAN COLLEGE Pagadian City, Zamboanga Del Sur 2017-2019

Experience

Radio Broadcaster/ Journalist

2016-2017

ANG AKADEMYAN

The Official School Publication of Holy Child Academy

Divisions Schools Press Conference

2016-2019

Filipino Radio Broadcasting/Ang Akademyan/Ang Hiraya

A competition for journalism for both private and public elementary and secondary schools in the Philippines as per Republic Act 7079.

TV/Radio Broadcaster/ Journalist

2017-2019

The Capstoine/ Ang Hiraya

The Official School Publication of Saint Columban College - Senior Highschool Deparment.

Broadcasting Head

2018-2019

Ang Hiraya

The Official School Publication of Saint Columban College - Senior Highschool Deparment.

Staff Witer/Journalist

2019-2020

The Campus Access

The Official School Publication of BISU Balilihan Campus

Associate Editor-in-Chief

2020-2021

The Campus Access
The Official School Publication of BISU Balilihan Campus

Editor-in-Chief 2021-Present

The Campus Access

The Official School Publication of BISU Balilihan Campus

Vice President 2021-Present

Supreme Student Government BISU Balilihan Campus